<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
  <!-- What is Ambrosia? -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ThingDef[defName="Ambrosia"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A soft, rare fruit tied to stories of divinity, ascending to the other-side, and granting the curse of immortality. Ambrosia's taste matches the myth with its heavenly texture, subtle notes of sweetness, and wild rush of mind-bending chemicals that provide a mood-increasing chemical high. However, if eaten too often, it can generate a mild addiction.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <!-- Ambrosia High -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/HediffDef[defName="AmbrosiaHigh"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>Ambrosia's chemicals pervade the bloodstream, lifting the mood but noticeably lacking in radical powers of immortality. A damned shame indeed.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <!-- Think Ambrosia Error? -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName="AmbrosiaHigh"]/stages/li/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>Ahh, feed of the gods. It's incredibly sweet...</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <!-- Need Ambrosia -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/NeedDef[defName="Chemical_Ambrosia"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>Because of an ambrosia addiction, this person needs to regularly consume ambrosia to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <!-- Ambrosia Tolerance -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/HediffDef[defName="AmbrosiaTolerance"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A built-up tolerance to ambrosia. The more severe this tolerance is, the more ambrosia it takes to get the same effect.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <!-- Ambrosia Addiction -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/HediffDef[defName="AmbrosiaAddiction"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A chemical addiction to ambrosia. Long-term presence of ambrosia has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug.
\nWithout regular doses of ambrosia, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <!-- Ambrosia Withdrawal Error? -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName="AmbrosiaWithdrawal"]/stages/li/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>I feel so heavy and endlessly cold. Am I being punished? Just for some fruit?</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>
</Patch>