<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ThingDef[defName="SmokeleafJoint"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>Smokeleaf leaves prepared in small rolls for smoking. The drug improves mood, but also increases appetite, reduces focus and slows movement. Smokeleaf use can produce a dependency.\n\nJoints can be produced at a crafting spot without equipment, and are a fixture in many traditional low-industriousness cultures.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/HediffDef[defName="SmokeleafHigh"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>Smokeleaf's active chemicals spread within the bloodstream generating a soft feeling of fuzzy well-being.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName="SmokeleafHigh"]/stages/li/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>I'm, like, stoned, man.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/NeedDef[defName="Chemical_Smokeleaf"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>Because of a smokeleaf dependence, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/HediffDef[defName="SmokeleafTolerance"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A built-up tolerance to smokeleaf. The more severe this tolerance is, the more smokeleaf it takes to get the same effect.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/HediffDef[defName="SmokeleafAddiction"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A chemical addiction to smokeleaf. Long-term use of smokeleaf has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug.
\nWithout regular doses of smokeleaf, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName="SmokeleafWithdrawal"]/stages/li/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>I'm scared, sad, and in desperate need of another hit. This, like, sucks, man.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>


</Patch>